Michael Abaniwo

08076578993 | michaelabaniwo@gmail.com 12, Obadina Street, Abule-Oja, Yaba, Lagos, Nigeria

SKILLS

- Experience in ICT operation.
- Basic operation of HTML, CSS and JavaScript languages.
- Basic Web development with HTML and CSS.
- Trained Entrepreneur.
- Great Teaching ability with experience.
- Experience in Product Marketing and sale.
- Managerial skills and event planning

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Certified and Trained Entrepreneur, with a successful track record in ICT operation, aquarium construction, aquaculture management, marketing and sales ability and a great experience in teaching. Trained in the basic use of HTML, CSS and JavaScript by Frontend Masters.

EDUCATION

09/2016 - 09/2019 **University of Lagos, Nigeria.** Akoka, Yaba BSc. Marine Biology

WORK HISTORY

03/2020 - 02/2021 (NYSC)

Ministry of Natural and Mineral Resources, State Secretariat, | Osogbo, Osun State, Nigeria Administrative Assistant; where I was involved in report preparation, documentation and records management. I also had the opportunity to be involved in the awareness and study of the mineral resources available in the state.

01/2020

Raoatech Electromech and Robotics Company, | Lagos, Nigeria

Graduate Assistant in technology and robotics; where I got some experience in CCTV camera installation and educating students on the use of arduino in robotics.

10/2018 - 01/2019

Department of Marine Sciences UNILAG | Lagos, Nigeria

Industrial Trainee (SIWES); where I constructed Aquariums with ornamental designs, carried out Aquaculture maintenance and sold well packaged smoked catfish with marketing skills learnt.

08/2016 - 08/2016

Elegant Tutors | Lagos, Nigeria

Teacher; where I taught undergraduate students Biology and I taught Junior Secondary School Students Integrated Science and English.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certificate for a successful participation and outstanding achievements in the Impact Week Lagos 2018, an Entrepreneurial training. Presented by UNILAG and supported by Lufthansa German Airline.
- Certificate for successful participation in Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), First Aid, Automated External Defibrillator and Basic Life Support onsite training on 16th October 2019.
- Certification for participation during the 3-day free profitable Fish Farming Training, Fish Farming maintenance routines, Water quality management, Aquaria construction and Feeding in Aquaculture.